curriculumassociates.com 2017-06-06

# About us, Contact us, Request a Catalog - Curriculum Associates, LLC

Last Modified: May 4, 2017

Curriculum Associates, LLC (“Curriculum Associates” or “We”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit or are routed to the website [www.curriculumassociates.com](http://www.curriculumassociates.com/default.aspx) (the “CA Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. This policy applies to information we collect on the CA Website. Information collected through the i-Ready platform is governed by the [i‑Ready Data Handling Policy](http://www.i-ready.com/support/iReady_DataHandlingPolicy.pdf).

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using the CA Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the CA Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

Children Under the Age of 13  
The CA Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the CA Website. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It  
We collect several types of information from and about users of the CA Website, including information by which you may be personally identified, including information necessary to open an account; and information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access the CA Website, and usage details. 

We collect personal information directly from you when you provide it to us. If you provide us with your email address, we may attempt to contact you at that address regarding quote requests. We may also send you periodic emails about our products and our company. 

As you navigate through and interact with the CA Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns including, but not limited to, usage details, IP addresses, and other information. We use Google Analytics to track and store this information. This information helps us to improve the CA Website and to deliver a better and more informative experience. The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include cookies. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of the CA Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to the CA Website.

How We Use Your Information  
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information, to present the CA Website and its contents to you, to validate that User Content is only being provided by educators, to provide you notices, and to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide us the information.

Disclosure of Your Information  
We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy to contractors we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. We may also disclose personal information to a buyer or other successor entity in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Curriculum Associates’ assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Curriculum Associates about the CA Website users is among the assets transferred.

We may also disclose your personal information to comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request, to enforce our Terms of Use, or if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Curriculum Associates, our customers, or others.

Accessing and Correcting Your Information  
You may send us an email at [privacy@cainc.com](mailto:privacy@cainc.com) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement. If you request deletion of your User Contributions on the CA Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other CA Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the CA Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use.

Your California Privacy Rights  
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of the CA Website who are Curriculum Associates customers and are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@cainc.com](mailto:privacy@cainc.com) or write us at: Curriculum Associates, Attn: Legal Department, 153 Rangeway Road, North Billerica, MA 01862.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy  
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. The most recent privacy policy is posted on the CA Website. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting the CA Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

Contact Information  
To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [privacy@cainc.com](mailto:privacy@cainc.com).
